Tokoyami Towa - Palette
Composition, Arrangement, Mix, Mastering: niki
Illust, Storyboard, Animation: Kakage
Vocal, Lyrics: Tokoyami Towa
Nobody sees what it is blowing in the wind in this world
kaze ni fukarete dare mo kizukanu you
It is all monochrome, impossible to tell black from white
kubetsu ga tsukanai monokuro no sekai
Though I try to paint it up, all the colors never take hold
iro o tashite mo nani mo mienakute
I don't even feel alive, stuck in the middle of this all
marude watashi wa iki o tometeita
I've had enough
mou ii yo
I have a goal I want to reach though it is far
tookute mo kanaetai watashi wa
But this is my world, and I want to hold it dear with all my feelings
konna sekai omoi mo dakishimeteitai noni
On the canvas of my dreams I will continue to remain
yume no kyanbasu ni itsuzukeru imi wa
To see what's burning in my heart play out, my own story
kono mune ni kagayaiteiru sutoorii
Video, Compositing, 3DCG: Roly
To see what's burning in my heart play out, my own story
kono mune ni kagayaiteiru sutoorii
Logo Design: Wotoha (OFUTONE)
Vocal Direction: Neko Hacker (OFUTONE)
Vocal Recording: NNZN (OFUTONE)
While a silver platter is so well and truly meaningless
ataeru koto ni imi nado nai kedo
I stand scared of losing the pieces of the puzzle I have
hiroi atsumeta kakera ushinau no?
But then the freezing night finally begins to thaw
soshite yoru wa sono tsumetasa o
And reaches out to me with a new dawn
tokashite te o nobashita
That is enough
mou ii yo
I have a goal I want to reach though it is far
tookute mo todoketai watashi wa
I will accept it all and hold it dear together with all my tears
uketometeku namida mo dakishimeteitai noni
On the canvas of my dreams, what truly gives it all meaning
yume no kyanbasu ni kokoro komeru no wa
Is freely painting on the skies above my own story
kono sora ni egakidashiteku sutoorii
And so the freezing night finally begins to thaw
soshite yoru wa sono tsumetasa o
And reaches out to me with a new dawn
tokashite te o nobashita
This is enough
mou ii no
I have a goal I want to reach though it is far
tookute mo kanaetai watashi no
And this is my world, it is wrapped up together with all my words
konna sekai omoi mo kotoba de tsutsunda
On the canvas of my dreams, which I will continue to paint
yume no kyanbasu ni iro o tashiteyuku
In the same colors burning within my heart now
kono mune ni ima kagayaite
It may be all too weak and frail
tsuyokunakute mo ii
It may even crumble and fail
kowarekakete mo ii
My mind's desire still takes flight toward all eternity
kono kokoro wa towa ni habataite
It will resonate with and dye the future in my own palette
hibiku youni nurikaeteiku Palette